"lang"
{
"Language"	"english"
"Tokens"
{
"mimp1.radio.01" "<clr:188,188,188><I>Station 21, come in. This is Outpost 16. <delay:5><clr:188,188,188><I>Are you receiving? Station 21, do you read? <delay:8><clr:188,188,188><I>If anybody is receiving, please reactivate the listening post as soon as possible."
"mimp1.radio.02" "<clr:188,188,188><I>Station 21, do you copy? You're showing a strong signal again. Good to have you back online. We'll be able to monitor the Combine transmissions from here again. <delay:10><clr:188,188,188><I>Hang on... Oh shit, we're picking up heavy radio chatter. Looks like a Combine strike team is inbound on your position. <delay:18><clr:188,188,188><I>If you're still receiving, evacuate the area immediately and try to make your way to Outpost 16. Just follow the road. You can't miss it."
"mimp2.leader.welcome" "Doctor Freeman, welcome to our outpost. Please follow me, I have a proposition for you."
"mimp2.leader.brief01" "I am sad to say that after several votes, we have decided to regroup to a position further away from the Combine."
"mimp2.leader.brief02" "I would love to stay and fight, but I went out for it every time."
"mimp2.leader.brief03" "Not only a fierce warrior, I am also a master strategist."
"mimp2.leader.brief04" "There is a Combine train depot close by. If someone were to infiltrate it and cause the distraction, the rest could slip away."
"mimp2.leader.brief05" "I have presented this plan to my squad, but they are not ecstatic."
"mimp2.leader.brief06" "Even worse, I can not go myself, since the only way into the exit tunnels is a ladder - my only weakness."
"mimp2.leader.brief07" "So, you have a great opportunity, Doctor. With your legs, you can climb that ladder and help us all out."
"mimp2.leader.brief08" "I will show you the way. Try to keep up."
"mimp2.leader.goodbye01" "There you have it. Best of luck."
"mimp2.leader.goodbye02" "The ladder you need to climb yourself."
"mimp2.leader.warning" "Watch out down there! It might not be perfectly safe."
"mimp2.leader.nancy" "Stop being such a negative fancy!"
"mimp3.leader.reveal" "Oh, shoot."
"mimp3.leader.hill01" "Follow me, Freeman. The others are just over this."
"mimp3.leader.hill02" "You are welcomed to travel with us."
"mimp3.leader.rescue01" "Good thing we heard the commotion. No time for small talk. Let me help you up."
"mimp3.leader.rescue02" "Stand back from the door. I am going to open it!"
}
}
